# Soumyanil Das

Kolkata, West Bengal, India



soumyanil666@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/soumyanil-das

### **Summary**

I'm Soumyanil Das, primarily a Front End Developer from Calcutta who likes to mix code with creative, interactive and modern designs. I work across the full JavaScript stack, having worked as a freelancer initially and now working full time at CBNITS. Outside of work you can find me playing on the PS4 or chilling to music on Spotify.

#### **Experience**



#### **CBNITS**

Aug 2022 - Present (8 months)

Working as a Senior Angular Developer at Netskope as a contractor.

- Working as an SME for Homepage.
- Helping fix bugs and customer issues in Homepage, Reports and Netskope Advanced Analytics (using Looker)
- Working on new features for Homepage and Advanced Analytics.
- Helping write end to end test using Python and Selenium.

### © UI Developer

#### **CBNITS**

Sep 2021 - Aug 2022 (1 year)

Working as a Senior Angular Developer at Netskope as a contractor.

- Working as an SME for Homepage.
- Working on helping implement new feature in Netskope Advance Analytics (using Looker)
- Working on improving and maintaining Homepage and Reports pages on Angular10 and APIs in PHP Codelgniter
- Worked as an SME for CCI area and maintained and improved its UI pages and APIs.
- Worked on migrating Reports from AngularJS to Angular 10
- Writing Unit test for components and services using Jest
- Helping QE team with writing automation test in Pylark (Python)
- Helped with on-call

# Frontend Developer

#### **Capital Numbers**

May 2020 - Sep 2021 (1 year 5 months)

Worked with Vue and Ionic Vue to create interactive and modern UI/UX for web and mobile users which consumes a REST API made in Wordpress fetching data from a centralized casino database

### Frontend Developer

#### Logic Square Technologies

Aug 2018 - May 2020 (1 year 10 months)

Worked with Angular, Ionic 3/4 and Vue.js. Was given the responsibility of delivering web and mobile apps which would help clients in solving their business requirements.

### Fullstack Developer

Freelancer.com

Nov 2016 - Nov 2018 (2 years 1 month)

Worked as a Fullstack Javascript developer which includes Angular and Vue for Frontend, Ionic 4 for mobile app and Nest.js with MySQL for Backend

#### Trainee Developer

Logic Square Technologies

May 2018 - Aug 2018 (4 months)

Working with Angular 5 and Ionic 3

### Intern Web Developer

Heritage Institute of Technology

Sep 2016 - Nov 2016 (3 months)

NCoRe is a Simple, Multiplatform (web and app-based) and Interactive Information System that helps the rural underprivileged communities by empowering them to interact and collaborate among themselves and with other rural development authorities (sub- clusters, clusters etc.) to share their problems and search for solutions.

This is my first internship work. We are using Bootstrap for front-end and PHP, MySQL for the back end.

#### **Education**

### Heritage Institute of Technology

Master's Degree, Computer Application 2015 - 2018

### University of Calcutta

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science 2012 - 2015

### The Future Foundation School

High School, Science with Computer Science 1997 - 2012

#### Skills

JavaScript • Angular • TypeScript • HTML5 • RxJS • Jest • SASS • NgRx • Vue.js • Ionic Framework

### **Honors & Awards**



## Client Choice Award

May 2022 Netskope's Client Choice Award for 2022